http://www.steamtractionworld.com/privacy-policy.htm

Steam Traction World Privacy Policy
Steam Traction World Privacy Policy
Updated 21st May, 2018
This privacy policy sets out how Steam Traction World uses and protects any information that you give Steam Traction World when you use this website.
Steam Traction World is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.
Steam Traction World may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from 21st May, 2018 and covers the introduction of GDPR, in the UK on 25th May, 2018
What we collect
We may collect the following information:
name
contact information including email address
other information relevant to customer area
We currently collect your information via:
Contact Forms
Website (Mailchimp) Signup Form
Customer enquiry
Enquiries through Direct Email, Social Media, telephone or post.
Customers interested in us - job applications, CV’s etc
What we do with the information we gather
We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:
Internal record keeping.
We may use the information to improve our products and services.
We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers, events or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided. Every bulk mailing, we have ever sent out, has had an 'unsubscribe' link at the bottom of the email. If you do not wish to receive any more info from us you can click on this link at anytime and we’d remove you from our database.
From time to time, We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. This may be because of a specific news or event at Steam Traction World.
Security
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
How we use cookies on our Website
A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.
We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.
Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.
You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.
Links to other websites
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
Controlling your personal information
You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:
If you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at info@steamtractionworld.co.uk
We will not sell, distribute or loan your personal information to any third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so.
You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998, GDPR 2018. A fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to Steam Traction World.
If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
STEAM TRACTION WORLD
General Data Protection Regulations (2018)
Website Design by Nick Price Creatives - Sitemap • Privacy Policy
